you stop?
Oh, no, no, no,
Dreaming on!
Whoa!
Sir Kin'emon!
Sir Denjiro!
Godspeed ahead!
And to you as well!
We're out of money!
What now? Oops.
Oh, no.
What about dinner?
Yes.
Here's the plan.
Let's head to town and beg.
Please, no. Whoa.
It must have been hard.
I'm sorry.
King.
Don't stop.
We must go on.
Izo?
This may be our end.
Are you certain?
I've missed too many chances
for a meaningful death.
Alright, onward.
Okiku!
Die alongside your lord if you like,
but wouldn't you rather
conquer the world with me?
I know that you, samurai,
are famously loyal,
and if any of you have the courage
to challenge us, you have my respect.
I speak for all our ninjas
as head of the Oniwabanshu;
I pledge my forces to you.
We are 5,000 strong.
The samurai, who also number 5,000 in
total, pledge their allegiance as well.
I welcome you.
Our lord is dead.
Well, whatever.
That's great, man.
I'm so glad we're not enemies.
I didn't want to have to kill you.
Here's to a bright future!
How dare you call yourself
samurai after that! Not now, boss!
We gotta lay low!
Well, what do you know?
That idiot's flunkies couldn't
wait to get a new master.
Nice thinking, Kaido.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Our forces are already
coming together nicely.
Let me go! Hey! Ow!
Don't be a jerk!
Keep those slippery Straw Hats restrained!
If you think you've
won, you're dead wrong!
As long as Shinobu escapes,
we still have a chance!
Forgive me, Onami.
I'm going ahead.
I'll be fine, just save Mama!
Lord Odin knew from the start, taking
down Orochi doesn't change anything!
For 20 years, Kaido has been our true
enemy, the only target that matters!
There's no Shogun in Wano now.
All his samurai, all his ninja,
all his men will serve me.
The people in the flower
capital don't know a damn thing.
They're dancing the night away in
what'll be their final hours of freedom.
Because I'll say one thing, I've
always had my doubts about you.
It's hard for me to believe that you're
the son of a man like Kozuki Oden.
You're nothing but a whimpering coward.
That's not true!
This execution serves to bring an end
to the land of Wano as you know it.
I've been thinking back to the day 20 years
ago, when we met in the burning castle.
I asked a question you never answered.
Oh, someone, help.
Now tell me your name, dammit.
Spideless brat!
Father!
Somebody help!
If you're not the son
of Kozuki Odin and Toki,
then I'll cancel your
execution immediately!
And let you walk free—you
would have my apologies;
it would have been a
great mistake on my part.
But
if it wasn't an heir?
And you are their son?
You'll suffer the same fate as Odin!
And die by my hand.
Now
brat—one last time!
last time
What is your name?
See how generous the commander could be?
Don't worry, kid.
Your dad won't be ashamed of you.
He's been dead for years.
Come up with a funny name for us, okay?
You got this.
No one will look down on you if
you have to lie, Lord Momonosuke.
Just please stay alive.
What?
Are you serious?
That boy is the real Kozuki Momonosuke?
Of course he is!
Hoden's retainers are alive, too!
What?!
The enemy!
Get out of my way!
You mean the samurai made it?
All of them are alive? Really?
So Odin's sacrifice was
worth it. That's great!
He did it!
Why are we standing around?
Let's get out there and rescue Momonosuke!
I can't wait!
If the Akasai and I are here, then
that means I get to meet them!
Put me down, Yamato!
Huh?
Wait a sec.
What did you just call me?
Master Yamato, please stop!
Master Yamato and Suha and Luffy are
heading to the floor, moving fast!
You mean the performance floor?
Yes, sir!
We're closing in to catch them right now!
No, don't bother.
You know Matt's best.
Beating up my men now, are you?
Yamato!
I'm gonna bust you up!
Puss up! Stop!
We can't go this way!
It's too scary! Too scary!
This whole mission is scary!
But you heard them!
They're gonna kill Momo!
Oh, I know, but look!
Those giants!
They'll gobble us up!
They'll grind our bones
to make their bread!
We can do this, pal!
Even an emperor of the sea
couldn't take us out, right?
If Big Mom can't beat General
Franky, then no one can!
I don't care!
They're still too scary!
Don't freak out!
You're scaring me too!
Take Commander Jumper!
What's your order?
Retreat! Retreat!
What is your deal?
You're a samurai, huh? So what?
Because I'm going to
be king of the pirates!
Your father's a great man.
Momonosuke, one day you
will rule this land.
Then you'll understand.
You want to know the
meaning of your name? Yes!
I want you to be strong,
but more than that you should be
compassionate and broad-minded
Momo
It's a word that means perilous among men
You want my name?
It's Kozuki Momonosuke.
Hear me now!
Now I shall become the
Shogun of the land of Wano!
Of course you will, my lord!
I'm coming, Lord Momonosuke.
I promise I'll save you.
It seems the future of
Wano is in good hands.
We're almost there, Luffy!
Let me take these things off.
I promise, right? Yes, please.
But, uh, just in case, could
you throw them far away?
I don't think they'll
explode, but I can't be sure.
What's wrong with this country?
You're nothing but fools!
Father... Mother...
I am a disappointment
to you and to myself.
All I wanted was to be able to face you
with pride when we
reunited in the afterlife.
Iori, I wish I could see you again.
If even for a moment, I don't want to die!
Curse these tears!
Osamu and I should not
cry in front of others!
I am ashamed!
You took them off!
Luffy, it was true!
Go to hell, you stupid
ugly cow, gorilla bastard!
You really were going to kill me!
Where the hell did that
explosion come from?
Somebody figure it out right now!
Well, that settles it.
I've made up my mind.
You're not my father anymore!
Whatever trouble you're starting,
you better knock it off!
Come back, Yamato!
I'll crush you!
I'm glad we weren't too late, but
this isn't our fight to start.
That honor belongs to somebody
else, and you know who it is.
Yaku!
Hey!
Huh?
The Akazaya Samurai!
Where did they come from?
What?
The kings of the minx?
They're still alive?
They won't lose to a bunch of ghosts!
Izo!
Hey, you shit-heads!
Stop drinking and come kick some ass!
The party is up!
We're under attack!
It's you, Kyoshiro!
Kaido!
I'll kill you as many times as it takes!
Surrender your name.
Thee as a child.
The blades you wield are powerless.
They can't cut me.
Stake your very lives on this attack.
Odin.
Leave the land of water.
And never return.
Tsunami.
Holden Two-Swords die!
Paradise Ports die!
I feel it in the old scar Odin gave me.
How did the blades pierce my flesh?
Why does it burn?
You have underestimated my samurai, Kaido.
They can call me a hero or a fool.
They can even forget me if they so please.
But...
No matter what, my spirit will live on!
This shouldn't be possible.
Are they using Ryu like Odin did?
Pierce him through!
It's really them, the Akazai
Samorais. Yeah, I know.
Cool, huh?
This is my second bloody party in a row.
You're not dead down
there, are you, Kaido?
Now get in there!
Slaughter those Akazara rats!
So Straw Hat and the
others were just decoys.
They were coven for the
samurai surprise attack.
Keep your eyes peeled, men.
If those samurai snuck in,
there might be more intruders.
You bet there are!
Yeah.
Listen, you spineless thugs.
I won't let you lay a
finger on those samurai.
Come on, let's get in there and fight!
I could go for some payback, too!
I found you, Yamato!
Now get rid!
Headbutt!
O .T.
How dare you clobber me with that club!
I am supposed to be
your ally and now you're
running around and playing
hero with Straw Hat.
That's ever ever so messed up
There's nothing messed up about it,
but this is the day that I
will become Kozuki Oden Huh?
You totally lost me.
Ah, you're such an idiot
Master Yamato we need
your help the commander
just got attacked by the
Akazaya samurai All right,
we've got invaders running
all over the place.
Whatever you're doing now is not the time.
I disagree.
I'm not your ally anymore.
I am your enemy, in fact.
And I don't care if my father dies. What?
More chaos, I see.
Never a dull moment at this party, huh?
Come, go!
Alpha, I die!
Wait a minute.
That's not good.
Did she notice Luffy?
I can't deal with Big Mom!
I got a job to do!
It's Draw Hat Luffy!
I have you now!
Faulty...
Mortar!
You ready, Carrot?
It's time to go!
Right!
You're in for it now!
Black balls!
Whoa, buddy! What did you do?
This is gonna hurt!
And I got something too!
One squirm cloud coming your way!
Alley cloud?
Epo!
Ectoclasm Center!
Nailed it!
You think you can kick dirt
in the face of my family?
You think I was going to let you live?
I came here for you.
That is to say, I came here to kill you!
Straw Hat!
What brings you to the land of Wano?
You don't actually think you
can take down Kaido, do you?
What a laugh, you little kidder.
That's not why I'm here!
Luffy!
Mr.
Straw Hat Man, what did you say?
If that's not it, then why?
I won't stop at Kaido.
Orochi said that after 20 years,
the Akazaya Samurai would
come to get their revenge.
Everyone thought he was
just being paranoid.
Then one by one, the pieces came together.
But even Orochi didn't think
you would team up with pirates.
It seems they were among the so-called
ghosts appearing at Odin Castle.
Reports from Punk Hazard.
The battle in Dressrosa.
Your allies in Zou.
All threads that were tied
together by the Straw Hats.
Funny how it all worked out.
I've been eyeing Straw Hat for some time,
and yet there you were,
hiding in his shadow.
Some of you held out for 20 years.
Some leapt forward in time.
and you gathered an
impressive army but watch
out cuz pirates will stab you in the back.
The second Straw Hat realizes you're
gonna lose; he'll turn tail and leave you.
Besides, I've already taken him down
a peg once he's useless as an ally.
I have heard more than enough
of your baseless slander.
Sir Luffy is nothing like you.
You Kaido, Onuchi, and all
of your stupid friends too.
You're getting your asses kicked.
Every last one of you.
You mark my words.
He will stand at the
pinnacle of this sea someday.
Even if every last one of us dies.
Sir Luffy will remain.
Jaybreak will come to
the land of Wano again.
It shall be.
Because that's what we promised our lord.
It's going to be an Alto war!
Awfully cocky, aren't you?
What are you going to do with
just a few hundred troops?
What she said, idiot!
Ta-da-da-da-da!
Yes, sir.
It's an emergency!
Thousands of intruders are pouring
in from the back of the castle!
Whoa!
That's impossible!
Let's go!
All right, fine.
If that's what you want.
Come on, I can do this
all day. Is that a joke?
The only joke here is you!
Samurai.
Cezara Judo!
We are here to help you!
This is point C!
The samurai who got caught in
the flower capital are here!
They're teaming up with the prisoners
from Udon and kicking our butts hard!
Let's keep it up.
We don't want to fall behind.
What a gentleman you are.
Clearing the way for us.
You have my thanks.
I'm not here to help you out.
I'm here to take revenge on
Kaido, and that's the end of it.
If you get in my way, I'll
crush you just like anyone else.
Well, at least you warned me.
Vroom!
Go to hell!
Amputation!
And shadows.
These pirates that Sir Kinamon
brought are really something.
I think we can win this.
Come on, you guys.
What's the deal?
The former warlord law
just showed up, too.
We're getting overwhelmed out here.
The enemy troops are teaming up.
What do you say?
Master Queen!
You guys have more bad news?
There's enemies at the
entrance to the island.
Marco the Phoenix and Perospero
have joined forces and they...
Ah!
Watch out! Just say it!
Don't leave me right there!
Candy prison!
You gotta be kidding me!
Sure wasn't expecting
those two to team up!
All right, it's time
to hunt some beasties.
Look if they stick with
me and this will be easy.
I'll make them all candy men soon enough.
Wait and see.
Alright you drunk
assholes, the party is off!
Time to stop eating and kick some ass!
Grab your weapons and go!
We've got a raid on our hands!
It begins!
Kaido is out of the picture.
But there are still three
lead performers down there.
I must be patient.
Please hold on, Lord Momonosuke.
I promise I'll find a way to save you.
Everyone!
Let us reclaim the land of Wano!
I heard what you said, Straw Hat.
You're gonna kick my ass, huh?
I accept your challenge.
Let's see what you're made of.
You're about to face the strongest
military power in the world.
You have my face!
Same to you.
I'll catch up later.
Damn that wind.
Sobered me right up.
A fight this epic!
Should be out of the open.
Reminds me of the last time we fought.
How do you expect to win this fight?
Now that Odin is dead.
We don't have Odin, but there's
something else we do have.
We were sure that Yugarra
would turn into a dragon,
which means we would
have to fight outside.
Huh?
We have no fear.
Red Heart anticipation
burns in our hearts.
Our fury is about to be
unleashed on Yugarra.
Ha, the meek tribe.
Damn straight.
They're the finest warriors
our kingdom has to offer.
The snowfall is quite mild.
The sky is clear and the full moon's out.